Clow is an incredibly intuitive design tool that allowed me to move the design of my spring-summer
collection forward in the most incredible way.
It enabled me to take the roughest of sketches and, through pattern drafting in 2D, really
explore the shapes and fits that I wanted to make.
A truly revolutionary stage for me was taking these flat garment shapes and being able to
digitally sew and drape them into a 3D rendering.
Within minutes you can see a 3D image of what you're designing and make alterations on those
small decisions that make a design special.
Also being able to look at the same garment simulated in different materials and different
patterns.
Then seeing how those choices alter the drape and look and spirit of a garment was truly
revolutionary.
A truly revolutionary stage for me was taking these flat garment shapes and being able to
digitally sew and drape them into a 3D rendering.
This is something that I absolutely love.
That just hits you right in the head.
It's a truly revolutionary design.
For the size of my store it's really like a studio to give it your all.
The state of the art is to take a glance at how much you have of this piece and go,
there's a great variety of stuff you can develop over the years to see how well it
stands.
So the 3Darenting is definitely a Bothy style fabric so you can see how different, how
it's layered and how it's designed.
Making it a 3D pattern was really cool.
And it's really clever and it's a piece that I've kept in my experience for years.
I think it's a really interesting model because it's such a beautiful design, but
it's really convenient to have.
It's a one-of-a-kind process that you can create on your own.
I'll see you guys in the next one.
Bye-bye.
Bye.